(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
はじまってしまったら...
Once it's already started...
やるしかないやろがい！
You've just gotta do it!
おらんのチャンネルは〜
Our channel is...
スバちょこるなたん スバちょこるなたん
Subachocorunatan, Subachocorunatan
スバちょこるなたん はじまるよ〜
Subachocorunatan is starting now!
地獄で会おうぜ！スバちょこるなたん
作詞：七条レタス 作曲・編曲：D.watt
Let's meet in Hell! Subachocorunatan
Lyrics: Shichijou Lettuce | Comp/Arr: D.watt
地獄から来たスバちょこるなたん
Subachocorunatan, came from hell
地獄で会おうぜ！
Let's meet in hell!
ちゅわ！スバちょこるなたんのツッコミ担当！
Chuwa! Subachocorunatan's straight-man!
どんなボケも切り捨てごめん
No mercy for any silliness
恐怖の極卒マネージャー 大空スバルだ！
Terrifying hell-warden manager, Oozora Subaru!
ちょこ！スバちょこるなたんの限界担当！
Choco! Subachocorunatan's simp-limit!
地獄を燃やす天帝の扇動師
Heavenly instigator who sets hell ablaze
恐怖の極卒保健、癒月ちょこですわ！
Terrifying hell-warden nurse, Yuzuki Choco!
んなぁい！スバちょこるなたんのバブ担当！
Nnaai! Subachocorunatan's baby!
悪魔も寝る甘いの天才
Genius of sweetness that puts devils to sleep
恐怖の極卒お姫様 姫森ルーナんなならぁい！
Terrifying hell-warden princess, Himemori Luna!
はい！スバちょこるなたんのゲラ担当！
Hai! Subachocorunatan's laugh-box!
どんなボケも全肯定
Total affirmation for any joke
恐怖の極卒懲教官 獅白ぼたんです！
Terrifying hell-warden discipline officer, Shishiro Botan!
今日の具合はどんなかな？
How's the condition today?
正気の内に覚悟しな
Steel yourself while you're still sane
産地直送 地獄の空気
Direct from the source, the air of hell
まじー！
It's bad!
ヘイ お待ち！
Order up!
チャンネル変えて 今なう地
Change the channel, it's Hell Now
うちらは一大事
We're a big deal
いっせーのーで
One, two, and...
地獄の釜を振るえ！
Stir the cauldron of hell!
そしたらいんだこの感じ
It's better that way
やるしかないやろがい
You've just gotta do it
地獄の天国より
Better than a heaven in hell
近所の地獄 前向けば無限の娯楽
Neighborhood hell, look ahead for endless fun
振り向けばこの手が届く
Look back and it's within reach
愛せよ奈落 俺たちヒキと呼んで
Love the abyss, call us hikikomori
スバちょこるなたん...
Subachocorunatan...
はじまるよ〜
It's starting now!
はじまるよ！！！
It's starting!!!
地獄から来た
Came from hell
地獄に落ちるぞ
Gonna fall into hell
地獄はいいとこ
Hell is a nice place
ここが地獄か お邪魔します
So this is hell? Excuse me for intruding
んなぁ、なんなのこの音！耳が腐るんなぁ！
Nnaa, what is this sound! My ears are rotting!
そうだよねルーナ！ほら、ストップ！
I know, right, Luna! Hey, stop it!
ちょっとガチ！見て見て！地獄一うまい手料理！
Seriously! Look, look! The tastiest cooking in hell!
もうやめろやめろ！総じて地獄なんだよな！
Stop it, stop it! It's all just hell, isn't it!
チャンネル変えて 今なう地
Change the channel, it's Hell Now
うちらは一大事
We're a big deal
いっせーのーで
One, two, and...
地獄の釜を振るえ！
Stir the cauldron of hell!
どうしたらいいんじゃ　この感じ
What should I do about this feeling?
行くしかないんやろかい
I guess I have no choice but to go?
遠くの天国より
Better than a far-off heaven...
近所の地獄　前向きは無限の娯楽
Is a nearby hell; being positive is infinite fun.
振り向けばこのテトラポット
If I look back, this tetrapod...
目指せ極楽　オレたちヒトと呼んで
Aim for paradise! Call us humans.
スバちょこるなたん
Subachoco-Lunatan
あじまうよー
It's starting!
地獄で会おうぜ！スバちょこるなたん
Let's meet in hell! Subachoco-Lunatan
あじまうよー
It's starting!
虎視眈々
Koshitantan
不安覗く予報士　甘く蕩けたノイズ
A weather forecaster peeking at anxiety; sweet, melting noise.
脳内暗示　泣かすキャンディ
Intracranial suggestion; a candy that makes you cry.
偉大なアイの冒涜　計画的な反抗
Blasphemy of great love; a planned rebellion.
攻めの網　Gimme your candy
An offensive net; Gimme your candy.
二人きりだけの世界　混ざり重なるダイム
A world for just the two of us; a mixing, overlapping dime.
君の意を攫う We jump high
Snatching your intentions; We jump high.
受け入れて完全なクライ　這うのライン　裸のアイ
Accept the perfect cry; a crawling line, naked love.
魅惑 1, 2, 3　君を単純に
Fascination 1, 2, 3; Simply make you...
奪い去ってしまう衝動　理性的感情
an impulse to snatch you away; rational emotion.
Can you feel もっと感情に
Can you feel? More emotionally...
強く求めて壊して Run, run, run
strongly desiring, breaking it; Run, run, run.
君と 1, 2, 3　ずっと Eyes on me
With you 1, 2, 3; Always eyes on me.
止まらない鼓動　奇跡的情状
A heart that won't stop; miraculous conditions.
交差するもっと深くに
Intersecting even deeper.
堕ちて Down, down, down
Falling Down, down, down.
厳然な存在証明　必要なんてないの
A solemn proof of existence? There's no need for that.
欲しがっちゃう意味　甘い甘い甘いキャンディ
The meaning of wanting it; sweet, sweet, sweet candy.
震え止まらない症状　禁断のアレそれ
A symptom of uncontrollable shaking; that and this forbidden thing.
全身の歓喜 Let's show you and me
Joy of the whole body; Let's show you and me.
音を走る閃のバイブ　なり響く野望のチャイム
A flash of vibe running through the sound; the chime of ambition ringing out.
君に触れその瞬間オーバー
Touching you, that moment is over.
いらない全てはいらない　なんて言わないでよ Be mine
I don't need it, I don't need anything—don't say that; Be mine.
誘惑 1, 2, 3　君が最高に
Temptation 1, 2, 3; You're the best...
連れ去ってしまう情譲　飛び越えた想像
giving in and carrying you away; imagination surpassed.
Tighten me さあ You're going to be
Tighten me; now, you're going to be...
共に果ててしまうまで Down, down, down
until we reach the end together; Down, down, down.
向かう先はオールナイト　手にするタイソー甘い
Heading for the all-nighter; the big prize in hand is sweet.
煌びやかな日々 Give me, give me そのキャンディ
Sparkling days; Give me, give me that candy.
震える生命プレイ　フリーザーエンゲージ
Trembling life play; freezer engage.
手に触れたその瞬間気づいて
The moment our hands touched, I realized...
交わる思い始まる In your way
our intersecting feelings are starting, in your way.
繰り返し目を合わせた先で
Beyond the repeated glances...
弾けて飛ぶ世界は今上
the world that bursts and flies is now supreme.
君を手に入れる So it's time
I'll have you, so it's time.
中指を立てたこの合図
This signal with the middle finger raised.
魅惑 1, 2, 3　君を単純に
Fascination 1, 2, 3; Simply make you...
奪い去ってしまう衝動　理性的感情
an impulse to snatch you away; rational emotion.
Can you feel もっと感情に
Can you feel? More emotionally...
強く求めて壊して Run, run, run
strongly desiring, breaking it; Run, run, run.
君と 1, 2, 3　ずっと Eyes on me
With you 1, 2, 3; Always eyes on me.
止まらない鼓動　奇跡的情状
A heart that won't stop; miraculous conditions.
交差するもっと深くに
Intersecting even deeper.
堕ちて Down, down, down
Falling Down, down, down.
はい、ということで、
Yes, so...
本日は癒月ちょこ生誕祭にお越しいただき
thank you for coming to the Yuzuki Choco
ありがとうございます！
Birthday Celebration today!
今回のハッシュタグはこちら！
This is today's hashtag!
#癒月ちょこ生誕祭2024
#YuzukiChocoBirthday2024
みんな、いっぱい呟いてください。
Everyone, please tweet a lot.
後で覗きに行きます。
I'll go check them out later.
そして、みんな！
And, everyone!
見て見て、このステージ！
Look, look at this stage!
凄くないですか？
Isn't it amazing?
アデュー、サロー
作詞・作曲：FLG4
Adieu, Salow
Lyrics/Composition: FLG4
いっそ　塵になって
I'd rather turn to dust
転がってたいけど
and just roll around, but
みっともないから
it’s unsightly, so
口から出る「大丈夫」
"I'm okay" spills from my mouth.
透明な街をすり抜け
Slipping through the transparent city,
傷跡曝したまま
scars exposed as they are,
耳障りメトロのメロディー
a grating metro melody.
こんな僕も肯定して
Affirm even someone like me.
感情も　心臓も
Neither emotions nor the heart
値段がつかないね
can be priced, right?
エンドレスな　蜃気楼
An endless mirage.
いくらですか　幸せとは
How much does it cost, this thing called happiness?
かみさま　うざったい恥を捨てたら
God, if I discard this annoying shame,
並べた嘘にキスしよう
let's kiss the lies I've lined up.
I love U　最低編の楽園さ
I love U, it's a lowest-tier paradise.
孤独と指を交ぜ　アデュー、サロー
Mixing fingers with loneliness, adieu, sorrow.
何者でもない僕を
Comfort me, at least,
せめて慰めてよ　アデュー、サロー
for I am nobody. Adieu, sorrow.
簡単なこともできずに
Unable to do even simple things,
息を止めて歩いた
I walked while holding my breath.
愛くるしいあの子はいつの間にか
That adorable girl, before I knew it,
笑えなくなっちゃった
could no longer smile.
まだ泣いてんだ　この人生は
Still crying, this life is
曇り模様　晴れ間探し
cloudy weather, searching for a break.
強がってるわけじゃない
I'm not just acting tough.
誰か僕を見てよ
Someone, look at me.
見つけて
Find me.
うざったい恥を捨てたら
If I discard this annoying shame,
並べた嘘にキスしよう
let's kiss the lies I've lined up.
I love U　承認に飢えた亡霊さ
I love U, a ghost starved for recognition.
負け惜しみで叫んだ　アデュー、サロー
Shouting out of sour grapes, adieu, sorrow.
何者でもない僕を
Me, who is nobody...
慰める奴はいない
...there's no one to comfort me.
アデュー、サロー
Adieu, sorrow.
私と Next Step へ
To the next step with me.
今宵はバラ色の
Tonight is a rose-colored...
夢をのせて　踊りましょう
Let's dance, carrying our dreams!
ROSE of the LAMP
作詞：志村真白(FirstCall) 作曲：EFFY(FirstCall)
Lyrics: Mashiro Shimura, Comp: EFFY
なんてったって触れたい
After all, I want to touch it,
知りたい　隠してた想い
I want to know these hidden feelings.
劇的でロマンティック
Dramatic and romantic.
時には甘く触れた　影絵のように
Sometimes touching sweetly, like a shadow play,
君にそっと囁くの
I whisper softly to you.
情熱の誘われるままに
As passion leads us...
ねえ
Hey...
本当の素顔見せて
Show me your true face.
もっと
More.
Gimme Gimme Love, Gimme Gimme Love
私のすべてを
My everything.
だって Crazy Crazy Love, Crazy Crazy Love
Because Crazy Crazy Love, Crazy Crazy Love
本気見せてあげる
I'll show you I'm serious.
アブラカタブラ　Hey!
Abracadabra, Hey!
君と出会えた奇跡に
To the miracle of meeting you.
アブラカタブラ　Hey!
Abracadabra, Hey!
愛を込めて　踊りましょう
Let's dance with love!
いつだって笑って　悩んで
Always laughing, worrying,
迷える日も
even on days when we're lost.
なんて素敵なドラマチック
What a wonderful dramatic story.
こうやって探して　感じて
Like this, searching, feeling,
重ね合わせて
overlapping...
君にちょっと近づくの
getting a little closer to you.
...を駆け抜ける風に ほら
...running through the wind, look.
本能で強く惹かれて
Being strongly attracted by instinct.
そう ギミギミLOVE ギミギミLOVE 溶かしてあげるわ
Yes, gimme gimme LOVE, gimme gimme LOVE, I'll melt you.
きっと ホリホリLOVE ホリホリLOVE 夢中 止められないの
Surely, holy holy LOVE, holy holy LOVE, I'm obsessed, I can't stop.
アブラカタブラ アブラカタブラ Hey!
Abracadabra, abracadabra, Hey!
こんな素晴らしい世界に
In such a wonderful world.
アブラカタブラ アブラカタブラ Hey!
Abracadabra, abracadabra, Hey!
君のために 踊りましょう
Let's dance for you.
もう ギリギリで ギリギリの 私の心（ここ）を
Already at the limit, at the very limit, my heart...
Baby 君だけに 君だけに 全部届けたいよ
Baby, only to you, only to you, I want to deliver everything.
もっと ギミギミLOVE ギミギミLOVE 私の全てを
More, gimme gimme LOVE, gimme gimme LOVE, all of me.
なんて クレイジークレイジーLOVE クレイジークレイジーLOVE 本気 見せてあげる
What a crazy crazy LOVE, crazy crazy LOVE, I'll show you my true self.
アブラカタブラ アブラカタブラ Hey!
Abracadabra, abracadabra, Hey!
君と出会えた奇跡に
To the miracle of meeting you.
アブラカタブラ アブラカタブラ Hey!
Abracadabra, abracadabra, Hey!
愛を込めて 踊りましょう
Let's dance with love.
魅力を隠す箱
A box that hides charm.
秘肌に香る 危なげな デンジャラス マリン メロウ
Scenting on secret skin, a dangerous, dangerous Marine Mellow.
I'm Your Treasure Box
※あなたはマリンせんちょうをたからばこからみつけた。
*You found Captain Marine in the treasure box.
Ahoy!
これあげる、君たちに。なんて言ってあげるべきかな？
I'll give you this. What should I say to you?
探してたんじゃない？船長を。
Weren't you looking for the Captain?
うふ、あ
Ehe, ah.
そんなにかぶりついちゃダメだぞ。…かな？
You shouldn't stare so intently... I guess?
お宝よりも魅力的なもの、見つけちゃった？
Did you find something more attractive than treasure?
いいじゃない
That's nice.
誘う 黄金と赤
Luring gold and red.
極上の 海賊の秘宝
The finest pirate's treasure.
それは 私
That is me.
艶（あで）が降れ漂う
Glamour descends and drifts.
香りも 何処かわからないで
Without knowing where the scent is coming from.
開けてみて
Try opening it.
セクシー世界一 スーパーピチピチ
Sexiest in the world, super fresh.
無茶で正常 捕まえたくない？
Reckless and normal, don't you want to catch me?
野暮な ゲット・ア・トレジャー メイビー・デスティニー
Boorish get-a-treasure, maybe destiny.
私の 甘さが欲しいでしょう？
You want my sweetness, don't you?
Ahoy! 出航！ 秘宝の鍵を
Ahoy! Set sail! The key to the secret treasure.
Ahoy! 出航！ 優しく刺して
Ahoy! Set sail! Pierce it gently.
Ahoy! 出航！ 宝庫の扉
Ahoy! Set sail! The door to the treasure vault.
マジで 早く 開けて！
Seriously, open it quickly!
きらめきたい花園で
In the garden I want to sparkle in.
回想に 溢れ舞う 溜息のキス
Overflowing with memories, the kiss of a sigh.
純白の薔薇が
The pure white rose...
萎れる前に
...before it withers.
耳澄ませ 激しい 七つの大海を
Listen closely to the violent seven seas.
彷徨い 未だ見ぬ 鍵爪
Wandering, the claw yet unseen.
砂利を しゃなり
Shuffling through the gravel.
貴方は どこから 何を探してんの？
Where are you from, and what are you looking for?
ラブ・プリズン・クラッチ・マイ・ギャラクシー
Love prison clutch my galaxy.
Open this box
Open it right now
I will scream
さあ 物語
Now, the story...
始め！
...begins!
泣くも黙るな 地の底
Crying, don't even be silent, the bottom of the earth.
…秘密 君たちも もう我慢できなくなっちゃう
...Secret, you won't be able to hold back anymore.
You're gonna own the pleasure made up for me
私のすべてを手に入れて
Take all of me.
Ahoy! 出航 Ahoy! 禁断の財宝
Ahoy! Set sail, Ahoy! Forbidden treasure.
Ahoy! 出航 Ahoy! 監視中でしょ？
Ahoy! Set sail, Ahoy! You're watching me, aren't you?
Ahoy! 出航 Ahoy! しわしわになっちゃう
Ahoy! Set sail, Ahoy! I'm going to get all wrinkled.
誰か助けて
Someone help me
マジで 炎上しすぎ
Seriously, it's flaming too much.
君たち 何考えてんの？
What are you guys thinking?
わかってるぞ 覚悟
I know, prepare yourselves.
だから 今すぐ 開けてよ
So open it right now.
宝箱
Treasure box
あなたを 待ってるわ
I'm waiting for you.
君！君たち！
You! You all!
開けてー！
Open it!
Baby don't stop 回る baby don't stop ねえねえ 誰のせいかな
Baby don't stop, spinning baby don't stop, hey, whose fault is it?
あ 待って それはやばいかも
Oh wait, that might be bad.
え なんで どこがダメですか？
Eh? Why? What's wrong with it?
失敗もいいや まいっか 徐々に時間をかけながら
Failure is fine, whatever, taking my time gradually.
怖いがいっぱいだ でもまぁ君ならいいのかな
There's so much fear, but I guess if it's you, it's okay.
ヤバい目 もっともっと 知らないラブを知った
Dangerous eyes, more and more, I learned a love I didn't know.
守りたいなら あっち行って
If you want to protect me, go over there.
嵌めてみたいなら こっちおいで
If you want to try to trap me, come here.
妄想しちゃおう 壁だってほら
Let's daydream, even the walls, look.
想像以上で 誰にだって
Beyond imagination, for anyone.
迷ってしまうのは なんでなんで
Why, why do I end up getting lost?
黙って逃げるのは 気にしないで
Don't mind me running away in silence.
ずっとずっと 二人きりで アンコントロール
Forever and ever, just the two of us, uncontrollable.
きっときっと ちゃんと全部 交換しよう
Surely, surely, let's exchange everything properly.
Baby don't stop 回る baby don't stop ねえねえ 誰のせいかな
Baby don't stop, spinning baby don't stop, hey, whose fault is it?
あと君の本音
And your true feelings.
え もっと これもダメですか？
Eh? More? Is this bad too?
いっぱいいっぱいで 乾杯だ 迷子に踊ってみませんか
I'm full, a toast, why don't we dance as lost children?
ヤバい差 成長か 答えはそのうち出るかしら
A dangerous gap, growth? I wonder if the answer will come soon.
世界で きっと僕ら 度肝を抜く選手になっちゃってるの
In the world, surely we've become players who take people's breath away.
守りたいなら あっち行って
If you want to protect me, go over there.
嵌めてほしいなら こっちおいで
If you want me to trap you, come here.
冷静な声明は ポイしちゃって OK
A calm statement, it's OK to just throw it away.
定型ライフはいらないのよ
I don't need a routine life.
冷めてしまうとか 女子じゃ
Cooling down, as a girl...
ビビって火照ったり 出ないこんな
Flinching, getting hot, this won't come out.
ずっとずっと 二人きり アンコントロール
Forever and ever, just the two of us, uncontrollable.
きっときっと ちゃんと全部 交換しよう
Surely, surely, let's exchange everything properly.
守りたいなら あっち行って
If you want to protect me, go over there.
嵌めてみたいなら こっちおいで
If you want to try to trap me, come here.
妄想しちゃおう 壁だってほら
Let's daydream, even the walls, look.
想像以上で 誰にだって
Beyond imagination, for anyone.
迷ってしまうのは なんでなんで
Why, why do I end up getting lost?
黙って逃げるのは 気にしないで
Don't mind me running away in silence.
ずっとずっと 二人きりで アンコントロール
Forever and ever, just the two of us, uncontrollable.
きっときっと ちゃんと全部 交換しよう
Surely, surely, let's exchange everything properly.
Baby don't stop 回る baby don't stop ねえねえ 誰のせいかな
Baby don't stop, spinning baby don't stop, hey, whose fault is it?
Baby don't stop 回る baby don't stop ねえねえ 君のせいだよ
Baby don't stop, spinning baby don't stop, hey, it's your fault.
曖昧なノイズ かき消して
Erase the ambiguous noise.
強情なこの声は 無力
This stubborn voice is powerless.
結ばず　目を逸らす
Without tying, looking away
Believe you 何度目の後悔に
Believe you, how many times of regret
Realize I feel the
もういいよ　期待すら馬鹿だ
Enough already, even expecting is stupid
退路が　閉ざされるね　懐かしもない
The way back is closed, no nostalgia
Ah Ah 夢に見る
Ah Ah, dreaming
Ne Ne 狂いそうよ
Hey hey, I'm going crazy
壮大に　美を描く筆
A brush that grandly paints beauty
触れないで　冷たくないの？
Don't touch, isn't it cold?
Shut up, give me おこがましい
Shut up, give me, it's presumptuous
相反する言葉に耳を塞ぐ
Closing ears to conflicting words
冗談ばっか　聞きたくないわ
Nothing but jokes, I don't want to hear it
愛想尽くして　Be sick of the world
Run out of patience, be sick of the world
曖昧それで　ひとり流して
Vague, then, letting it flow alone
情調の気配　自己犠牲も抜け
Sign of sentiment, even self-sacrifice is gone
操作性の虚に笑うよ
Laughing at the void of operability
自己陶酔しないで　Die out of life
Don't be narcissistic, die out of life
幻想に揺り動かされる
Being shaken by illusions
愛なんて逃げ口上して
Using love as an excuse to escape
悦を飲み　規制するの
Drinking pleasure, regulating
Believe you 自己に酔った言葉で
Believe you, with self-intoxicated words
I hate you I hate you
もういいわ　悦に溺れて
Enough already, drowning in pleasure
自分がないなんて　腐ればいい
Saying you have no self, you should just rot
Ah Ah 呆れるよ
Ah Ah, I'm appalled
Ne Ne それでいいの？
Hey hey, is that okay?
妥協で泳ぐ世界に
In a world swimming in compromise
幸あれと　吐き捨てるの
Wishing luck, I spit it out
Shut up, give me 煩わしい
Shut up, give me, it's annoying
押し付けられる価値観に酔う
Intoxicated by forced values
正論ばっか　聞きたくないわ
Nothing but moralizing, I don't want to hear it
夢語ってろよ　Be sick of the world
Keep talking about dreams, be sick of the world
曖昧それで　卑俗な言葉で
Vague, then, with vulgar words
良心の快楽　飲み干すの　No soul
Drinking up the pleasure of conscience, no soul
完敗だ　虚に笑うよ
Complete defeat, I laugh at the void
自己陶酔でいいね　Die out of life
Self-intoxication is fine, die out of life
預けられた心の鍵
The key to the heart entrusted
誰もがすぐ失くすの
Everyone loses it soon
嫌いと虚勢を張り
Pretending to hate, bluffing
笑み浮かべ　街を行くの
With a smile, walking the city
Shut up, give me おこがましい
Shut up, give me, it's presumptuous
相反する言葉に耳を塞ぐ
Closing ears to conflicting words
冗談ばっか　聞きたくないわ
Nothing but jokes, I don't want to hear it
愛想尽くして　Be sick of the world
Run out of patience, be sick of the world
曖昧それで　独り流して
Vague, then, letting it flow alone
情調の気配　自己犠牲も抜け
Sign of sentiment, even self-sacrifice is gone
操作性の虚に笑うよ
Laughing at the void of operability
自己陶酔しないで　Die out of life
Don't be narcissistic, die out of life
I wanna shut up　息苦しいわ
I wanna shut up, it's suffocating
愛想尽くして　Be sick of the world
Run out of patience, be sick of the world
はーい！ということで！
Haaay! So!
あずあずおめでとうございます！
Azu-azu, congratulations!
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
あずあず今日はありがとう！
Azu-azu, thank you for today!
しかも、この衣装！おめでとうございますは白雪の方で！あずあず本当にありがとうございます！
And this outfit! The congratulations are for 'Shirayuki'! Azu-azu, thank you so much!
てか、衣装！
I mean, the outfit!
え、何何？ちょこのさ、お誕生日のためにさ、おめかししてくれたの？ちょっと！
Eh, what what? For Choco's birthday, you dressed up for me? Hey!
そうですね。ちょっと、みずしーさん以外では初めてお披露目しますね。
That's right. It's the first time I've shown it outside of 'Mizushi' [my solo live].
ちょっ、ちょっ、ちょっ！見て見て！え、カメラさん、足下からちょっと！
Hey, hey, hey! Look, look! Eh, camera-san, starting from the feet!
ちょっ、足下... 私が主役じゃないですよね？いや、いいんですか？この...
Hey, the feet... I'm not the lead today, right? Is it really okay? This...
ゆっくりゆっくり。
Slowly, slowly.
えー、でも、めちゃめちゃ、え、待って、これ、え、可愛い！
Eh, but, it's so... eh, wait, this... eh, it's cute!
すいませ... やめてください！本当に！今日誕生日なのに！すげー被ってる。
I'm sorr... Please stop! Seriously! It's your birthday today! I'm totally upstaging you.
ちょ、もう本当に！お呼びいただけたことでも嬉しいですのに。
Hey, seriously! I'm happy enough just to be invited.
私のオリ曲歌って、一緒に踊ってくださって、もう、めっちゃ...
Singing my original song and dancing together with me, it's just, so...
いや、なんかもう、めっちゃかっこいい曲やし、セクシーやし、もう、ねえ！
No, I mean, it's such a cool song, and sexy, right!
いや、私もチョコ先生バージョンが聞きたかったし！
No, I also wanted to hear the Choco-sensei version!
すごくて、あの、特に
It was amazing, and especially...
ちょっと語っていいですか？あの...
Can I talk about it for a bit? Um...
チョコ先生が、もう、私と全然違う歌い方をされたので。
Because Choco-sensei, you sang it so differently from me.
あ、すごい！と思って。
I thought, "Ah, that's incredible!"
エッチく歌っちゃった。他にもね、そう。
I sang it a bit sexily. And there was also...
あ、もうありがとうございます。チョコ先生バージョンも聴けて。
Ah, thank you so much. Being able to hear Choco-sensei's version...
一緒に、しかもお披露目できて、嬉しいです。ありがとうございます。
...and perform it together for the unveiling, I'm so happy. Thank you.
いや、こちらこそありがとうございます。
No, the pleasure is all mine. Thank you.
え、じゃあさ、じゃあさ、
Um, so, you know,
チョコ、お誕生日だから、
since it's Choco's birthday,
チョコのお願い聞いてくれる？
would you listen to Choco's favor?
あ、何です？何でもしますよ！靴舐めます？
Oh, what is it? I'll do anything! Should I lick your shoes?
え、嫌です！そんなんじゃない！そんなんじゃない！
No, I don't want that! It's not like that! Not like that at all!
初めて言った...！
That's the first time I've said that...!
チョコ先生のその靴舐められるタイプですよ！
Choco-sensei, I'm the type who'd have their shoes licked!
なんなら！
If anything!
いや、もう、今日はもう、こんな素敵なね、
But really, since I received such a wonderful...
ものをプレゼントしていただいたので、何でもします。
...present today, I'll do anything.
え、じゃあさ...
In that case...
はい。
Yes.
じゃあチョコ、せっかくだから、
well, since we're here, Choco would...
巴様とお写真撮りたい！
...like to take a photo with Tomoe-sama!
あ、嬉しい！
Ah, I'm so happy!
可愛い！
How cute!
そんなん、いつでも撮りますよ！
I'll take photos with you anytime!
だって、こんなエッチな巴様、しかも3Dだなんて、
I mean, such a sexy Tomoe-sama, and in 3D no less...
なんなかないんだよ、みんな！
...it's a rare sight for everyone!
そう、さっきの色気は凄いです。
Yeah, your sex appeal earlier was amazing.
私、チョコ先生も、ここ、ここ、めっちゃ！
I think Choco-sensei, here, and here, it's just... wow!
もう練習してた時から、もう！
Ever since we were practicing, I was like...!
ここの、ああ...！みたいな、ああ...！みたいな。
All those "Ah...!" and "Ah...!" moments here.
すごい、こんなに、なんか本当に、
It's amazing, like, really...
チョコ先生って、もう、ずっと応援させていただいてますけど、
I've been supporting you for a long time, Choco-sensei,
色っぽいのに、この可愛いお茶目なところもたくさんあって、本当に...
but while you're sexy, you have so many cute, playful sides too.
あ、写真でしたっけ？
Oh, were we taking photos?
もちろん、もちろん。撮りましょう！
Of course, of course. Let's take them!
お写真、お写真！
Photos, photos!
どんなポーズがみんな良いんだろう？
What kind of pose would everyone like?
え、うーん。
Hmm, let's see.
え、さ、あの、背中合わせでパチン！
How about back-to-back, with a snap!
可愛い羽！
What cute wings!
羽、可愛いねー。
The wings are so cute.
お羽！
The wings!
あ、結構身長差ありますね、私たち。
Oh, we have quite a height difference.
ね、巴様。
Right, Tomoe-sama?
うん。
Yeah.
お身長おいくつなんですか？
How tall are you exactly?
私、ヒール込みで178なんですよ。
I'm 178 cm including my heels.
うわ！すごい！なんかいつもホロライブさんのライブとかだと大きいけど、
Wow! Amazing! I'm usually among the taller ones in Hololive lives...
もっとチョコ、めっちゃでかいからいつも！
...Choco is usually much bigger than everyone else!
えー！なんかすごい！新鮮、新鮮！
Whoa! This is amazing! So fresh, so fresh!
可愛い、ちっちゃいチョコ先生も可愛いですね、私と並ぶと。
Cute, a small Choco-sensei is also cute when standing next to me.
嬉しい！じゃあ背中合わせで。
I'm happy! Then, back-to-back.
背中合わせで、うんうん。
Back-to-back, mhm.
いい感じ！パチン！
Looking good! Snap!
あ、もう一回。パチン！
Ah, one more time. Snap!
ほらみんな、スクショタイムだぞー！
Look everyone, it's screenshot time!
なんだろう？パチン、パチンなんだ。
What is it? Snap, snap.
あの、アプリで触った時、巴様がパチンって言ってるやつ。
You know, the thing Tomoe-sama says in the app, "Snap!"
そうそう、あれ！あれ、すごく好き！
Yes, that! I really love that!
あ、ありがとうございます！
Ah, thank you so much!
撮れた？
Did you get it?
じゃあ、そこから上、腕を上にやって、
Then, from there, put your arms up and...
セクシーポーズ！
...sexy pose!
いい感じ！パシャ！
Looking good! Click!
おーいいの！
Oh, that's great!
すごーい！めちゃいいの！巨乳と巨乳が並んでます！
Wow! It's so good! Two big-breasted beauties standing together!
すごいことになってる、もう！ビッグバンですよ！
This is incredible! It's a Big Bang!
すごいですね！
It really is amazing!
わー、嬉しい！
Wow, I'm so happy!
わー、すごい！ありがとうございます、本当！
Wow, incredible! Thank you so much, really!
え、あとさ、あとさ、
And also, and also,
もうちょっとセクシーに！
let's do something a bit more sexy!
あ、いいよ！よいしょ。
Oh, sure! There we go.
座っちゃおうかな！
Maybe I'll sit down!
あ、いいよ！よいしょ。じゃあ、
Oh, sure! There. Then...
クンクン（？）...うん、こんな？
...how's this?
背中合わせ、ピタッ。
Back-to-back, pressed together.
うん、ポーズ？
Mhm, a pose?
あー、すごい！
Oh, wow!
うわ、可愛い！なんか私の方が悪魔っぽいね、衣装的に。
Whoa, cute! I look more like a devil because of my outfit.
確かに、可愛い天使、可愛い天使。
True, a cute angel, a cute angel.
え、めっちゃ可愛いです！
Wow, you're so cute!
うわー、めっちゃ絵になる！
Whoa, it makes for such a great picture!
嬉しい！え、可愛いー！
I'm so happy! Oh, so cute!
ニコリ！
Smile!
わー、もう、本当、こんな並べる日が来るなんて、3Dで。嬉しいです。嬉しい！
Wow, really, that a day like this would come where we stand side-by-side in 3D... I'm so happy. So happy!
ありがとうございます。時間足りたかな？撮れたかな？
Thank you so much. Was that enough time? Did you get the shots?
ね。よいしょ。
Right. Okay.
あー、では、本当におめでとうございます！
Ah, well, congratulations once again!
え、ありがとうございます！チョコ先生の誕生日なのに、
Ah, thank you! Even though it's Choco-sensei's birthday,
私が、なんかこうとっておきの、忘れられないお誕生日、
for me, it's such a special, unforgettable birthday...
私も今日、誕生日にしたいぐらいですね、もう！
...I feel like making today my birthday too!
えー、本当に！
Wow, really!
本当にありがとうございます！え、でも今日は歌って踊れて、すごい嬉しかった！
Thank you so much! But really, being able to sing and dance today made me so happy!
いや、こちらこそです、本当に。あの、頑張ってください。これからも応援しておりますので。
No, the same here, really. Um, please do your best. I'll continue to support you from now on.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
では、ありがとうございました！白雪巴でした。ありがとうございました！
Well then, thank you very much! This was Shirayuki Tomoe. Thank you!
え、巴様どこ行くの？
Eh, Tomoe-sama, where are you going?
え、あ、ん？何ですか？
Eh, ah, what? What is it?
いやいや、ちょっと、せっかくなんで最前列で見ようかと思って。
No no, I just thought since I'm here, I'd watch from the front row.
待って、待って、待って！いや、もう、絶対！
Wait, wait, wait! No way, definitely not!
いや、もう、袖で見てましたけど、もう、前で見たいと思ってたんで、もう。
I was watching from the wings, but I've been wanting to see it from the front.
巴様、チョコメイト達にそんな、もう興奮されちゃうから！
Tomoe-sama, the Choco-mates will get too excited if you do that!
あなたたち、前で見て失礼よ！
You guys, excuse me while I watch from the front!
巴様、こっち！
Tomoe-sama, over here!
そう、ちょ、ちょ、蝶々になってるから！蝶々のフリしてるから！
Yeah, I'm... I'm becoming a butterfly! I'm pretending to be a butterfly!
行ってきまーす！
Off I go!
はい、ということで。
Alright then.
いやーガチで見た、
Man, I really saw it,
トワ様めちゃめちゃエッチくて良かったよ～
Towa-sama was so sexy and great~
チョコの誕生日にも駆けつけてくれました、ということで。
She came to celebrate Choco's birthday as well, so...
続いてはね、
Next,
ちょっとチョコ、カッコよくなっちゃおうかな～ということで。
Choco thought she'd like to be a bit cool...
次の曲は、ま、チョコのね、
The next song is, well, Choco's...
今年のテーマというか。
theme for this year, you could say.
ヴィラン。聴いてください。
Villain. Please listen.
ヴィラン
作詞・作曲：てにをは
Villain
Lyrics & Composition: Teniwoha
きっと手を繋ぐ不条理でゾッとされる
Surely, held hands will be met with a shuddering absurdity
ラットレース抜けたら通報される
If I escape the rat race, I'll be reported
ミュータントじゃないただの僕さ
I'm not a mutant, I'm just me
XとかYとか
X or Y or whatever
べき論者様は善悪多頭飼い
The 'ought-to-be' moralists keep many heads of good and evil
僕が君を侵害するって言いふらしてる
Spread rumors that I'm infringing on you
Mr.Crazy Villain Villain 夜行性の花弁
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain, nocturnal petals
違う服着て君の前では
Wearing different clothes, in front of you
男子のフリする
I pretend to be a boy
拝啓 Dr.Durand-Durand 迎えに来てください
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand, please come pick me up
顔も知らない誰かにとって僕はもうヴィラン
To someone whose face I don't even know, I'm already a villain
ヴィラン
Villain
ヴィラン・ヴィラン
Villain, Villain
中途半端　挙げ句の
Half-hearted, and in the end...
ヴィラン
Villain
逸脱の性をまたひた隠す
Hiding away my deviant nature once again
雄蕊と雌蕊じゃ立ち行かないの ねえ
Stamen and pistil won't cut it, you know?
知ってんの？乱歩という乱歩という作家のこと
Do you know? Ranpo, the writer named Ranpo
造花も果ては実を結ぶ
Even artificial flowers eventually bear fruit
ぶるってんじゃねーよ多種多様の性
Don't be trembling, genders are diverse
悲しい悲しい話をしようか
Shall we talk about something sad, so sad?
ゼラチン質の体
A gelatinous body
Mr.Crazy Villain Villain 可能性に幸あれ
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain, may there be luck in possibilities
僕のハートは1LDK
My heart is a 1LDK apartment
嫉妬くらいはさせてよ
At least let me feel a bit of jealousy
拝啓 もっとヨロヨロ 微熱相手でいいのに
Dear, even a staggering, slight-fever partner would do
誰も知らない 知られたくない
Nobody knows, I don't want it known
皮膚の下
Under the skin
素晴らしい逆境と共に捧げる歌
A song offered along with wonderful adversity
骨まで響いてあれ悪辣に
Resonate to the bone, be wicked
残酷な街ほど綺麗な虹が立つ
The more cruel the city, the more beautiful the rainbow
猥雑広告に踊るポップ体の愛
Love in pop fonts dancing on vulgar advertisements
Mr.Crazy Villain Villain 夜行性の花弁
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain, nocturnal petals
違う服着て君の前では
Wearing different clothes, in front of you
男子のフリを
I'll pretend to be a boy
拝啓 Dr.Durand-Durand 僕だよ
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand, it's me
顔も知らない誰かにとって僕はもうヴィラン
To someone whose face I don't even know, I'm already a villain
ヴィラン
Villain
ヴィラン・ヴィラン
Villain, Villain
中途半端　挙げ句の果ての
Half-hearted, and in the very end...
ヴィラン
Villain
はい、ということで！皆様！
Yes, and so! Everyone!
チョコの重大告知1つ目！
Choco's first major announcement!
今年も有ります！どうぞ！
There is one this year too! Here it is!
癒月ちょこ誕生日記念2024、グッズ！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2024, Goods!
まずは詳細を見ていきましょう！こちら！
First, let's look at the details! This!
ドドン！
Ta-da!
Nardack先生描き下ろし、
Newly drawn by Nardack-sensei,
アクリルジオラマスタンド！
Acrylic Diorama Stand!
ということでね、今回は怪盗チョコテーマに描き下ろしていただきました。
So, this time it was drawn with a Phantom Thief Choco theme.
めちゃめちゃ良くないですか？
Isn't it super great?
こちらジオラマスタンドなんです。みんな飾れ！
This is a diorama stand. Everyone, display it!
そして2つ目は、こちら！
And the second one is, this!
ちょこ×悪魔のスウェット！
Choco x Devil's Sweatshirt!
ちょこの♡悪魔のスウェット！ということでね...
Choco's ♡ Devil Sweatshirt! And so...
こちらなんとワンポイント胸元にチョコメイト...
This has a Chocomate logo on the chest...
そしてね、背面にはNardack先生の...
And on the back, there's an illustration by Nardack-sensei...
めちゃめちゃおしゃれなイラストが。これはちょこのスウェット！
...a very stylish illustration. This is Choco's sweatshirt!
おしゃれで部屋着以外にも着れちゃうんじゃない？
It's stylish, so you can wear it as more than just loungewear, right?
そしてそして...
And then, and then...
タラーン！皆様お待たせいたしました。これ欲しかったんじゃないですか？
Ta-da! Everyone, sorry to keep you waiting. Didn't you want this?
魔導書風ポストカードアルバム。
A grimoire-style postcard album.
あ、間違えちゃった。魔導書風ポストカードアルバムということで。
Ah, I messed up. A grimoire-style postcard album!
みんなね、記念グッズとか買うときにポストカードがいっぱい溜まってるでしょ？
Everyone, you have lots of postcards piling up from buying anniversary goods and stuff, right?
ちょこがアルバム作ってやったから、その中にいっぱいしまって、後でいっぱい見返して！
Choco made an album for you, so put lots in there and look back at them later!
はい、そして...
Yes, and...
今年もあります！
We have them this year too!
癒月ちょこ書き下ろし台本耳攻めASMR！
ASMR with scripts written by Yuzuki Choco!
こちらね、ボイス3種類ございます。
There are three types of voices.
まず1つ目のボイスは「ちょこねえの罵倒意地悪ボイス」ということで。
First, we have "Choco-nee's Scolding & Mischievous Voice."
いやこちらはね、ちょこがちょっと罵倒しながら、ちょっとイタズラしちゃうんだよね。
In this one, Choco scolds you a bit and plays some tricks on you.
そしてそして、ちょこ先生の秘密の課外授業ということで。
And then, we have "Choco-sensei's Secret After-school Lessons."
まあみんなはね、ちょっとおサボりしてるちょっと生徒さんになっていただいて、ちょこ先生と秘密の課外授業しちゃうっていうエッチボイス。
You'll be a student who's skipping class, and you'll have secret after-school lessons with Choco-sensei. It's a spicy voice track.
そして最後、禁断のチョコボイスはね...
And finally, the "Forbidden Choco Voice" is...
こちらなんと、ちょっと時間も長めのちょっと耳攻めプラス、ちょっと色んなもの盛りだくさんのエッチボイスなのでまあちょっと楽しみに聞いててください。
This is a longer track featuring ear-focused ASMR plus lots of other things. It's a spicy voice track, so please look forward to it.
そして、フルセットの特典はこちら！ドンドンドン！
And here are the full set bonuses! Bam, bam, bam!
なんと今回久々にちょっと数量限定の直筆サイン入り箔押し複製メッセージ、箔押し特製メッセージ入りNardack先生描き下ろしポストカードが付いてくる！
For the first time in a while, it comes with a quantity-limited postcard illustrated by Nardack-sensei, featuring a handwritten signature and a foil-stamped message!
こちらね数量限定なので、皆様今回は頑張ってください。
Since it's quantity-limited, everyone, please do your best this time.
早めに早めにお願いします。
Please get it as soon as possible.
そして特典2つ目は！
And the second bonus is...
あの皆様がちょこのペットになっていただいて、ちょこ先生に飼われてみたらどうなっちゃうの？みたいなちょっとASMRボイスを撮ってみました。
An ASMR voice track where you become Choco's pet. What would it be like if you were kept by Choco-sensei? I recorded something like that.
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
はい。こちら通常、通常版は、あのちょこのサインとメッセージがちょっと箔押しの複製メッセージ、複製サインになってしまうのですが、その他の特典は変わらないので。
The regular version will have a foil-stamped printed signature and message, but all other bonuses remain the same.
はい皆様。
So, everyone...
争奪戦頑張れ！
Good luck with the sales battle!
はいということで、こちらはねライブ終了後に販売開始となりますので皆様待機しといてください。
And so, these will go on sale after the live show ends, so please be ready and wait.
そしてこの後は、皆様お待ちかねレッドカーペット！
And after this is the moment you've all been waiting for, the Red Carpet!
行くぞー！
Here we go!
はいということで、毎年恒例ちょこの誕生日にはこれが欠かせないよねということで。今年もやります！レッドカーペット！
And so, it's an annual tradition. We can't have Choco's birthday without this! We're doing it again this year! Red Carpet!
まあまあまあ、このレッドカーペットをご存知でない方は、今回初めてだよって方、はーい。
Well, for those of you who don't know about this Red Carpet, if this is your first time, raise your hand.
ちょっとご説明させていただきます。
Let me explain it a little bit.
まあねもう「俺、知ってるぜ」って方はどうぞ。
Well, for those of you who already know, please go ahead.
ということで皆様、見えるかな？今までみんなに慣れてもらったものがなんとドドーンと！
And so, everyone, can you see? What you've all been getting used to... Bam!
ちょこがね、この先の告知への道を作ってくれますということで。
Choco is creating the path toward the upcoming announcements.
うわーみんなありがとう！
Wow, thank you everyone!
では早速進んでいきましょう。
Now, let's proceed right away.
はいということでね、今回この新ステージもちょこのこのお誕生日のライブのために作っていただきました。はい、めちゃめちゃ...
And so, this new stage was also created especially for Choco's birthday live show. Yes, it's really...
ちょこ♡悪魔のスウェット
Choco ♡ Devil Sweatshirt
魔導書風ポストカードアルバム
Grimoire-style Postcard Album
記念ボイス
Anniversary Voices
フルセット購入特典
Full Set Purchase Bonus
誕生日記念フルセット
Birthday Anniversary Full Set
いや、良くないですか、このステージ？
Isn't this stage just great?
そしてね
And then,
なんと今回のサブネも
amazingly, this time's thumbnail too...
毎年お世話になっている、アンバサ先生に書いていただきました！
...was drawn by Ambasa-sensei, who helps me every year!
はい、ということでね
Yes, so anyway,
めちゃめちゃエッチでしょう？
it's super sexy, right?
そう、禁断の果実、食べてるんだよね
Yeah, I'm eating the forbidden fruit.
いいでしょう、いいでしょう？
It's good, isn't it?
そして、そして
And, and,
なんとね、この後も重大告知あります！
amazingly, there's a major announcement after this too!
いやあ、もうみんなね、楽しみにしてると思うんだけど
I'm sure everyone is looking forward to it,
チョコもね、早くお披露目したくてうずうずしてるよ
and Choco is also itching to reveal it soon.
さあ今回ね、ちょっとグッズの方も数量限定なので皆様、張り付いててね。
Now this time, the merchandise is limited in quantity, so please keep a close eye on it.
ということで
So,
せーの、ぴょん！
Ready, hop!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ということで、今回、重大告知第２弾！
So, this is the second major announcement!
今回も、チョコ、歌っちゃいました！
This time, Choco sang again!
禁断の果実テーマの、オリジナル曲！
An original song with a forbidden fruit theme!
Got Cheat!
世界一セクシーでかっこいいガチ恋、届けたいと思います！
I want to deliver the world's sexiest and coolest "serious love"!
この新曲が終わったら、なんと新曲のMV公開と
Once this new song is over, amazingly, the MV will be released,
メンバー限定ライブもあるので、皆様メンバーシップのご加入よろしくお願いします
and there will also be a member-only live stream, so please join the membership!
それでは、行きましょうか
Well then, shall we go?
Got Cheat
作詞・作曲・編曲：テッポウウオ(La'Joule)
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Teppouuo (La'Joule)
人ばかりの光
Lights full of people
月明かりの代わり
In place of moonlight
見下ろした街並み
The cityscape I looked down upon
少しも惹かれない
Doesn't attract me at all
嗅ぎつけなよ気持ち
Sniff out your feelings
この時間も惜しい
Even this time is precious
焦らすのも嗜み
Teasing is also a pleasure
そういうの今度でいい？
Is that okay for next time?
Guilty Pleasure
蜜もっと飲ませて
Let me drink more nectar
もっと言わせて
Make me say it more
恥ずかしい
How embarrassing
君はどこにでもいる Boy
You are everywhere, Boy
なのに胸がヒリつく Why?
And yet my chest stings, Why?
いけるところまで行かせて
Let me go as far as I can
揺れる輪郭も湿ってる Got Cheat
The swaying silhouette is also damp, Got Cheat
これはありふれている Lick
This is a commonplace Lick
だけど繰り返したい Words
But these are words I want to repeat
いけるところまで行かせて
Let me go as far as I can
甘い誘惑癖になってる Got Cheat
The sweet temptation is becoming a habit, Got Cheat
君のせいでも僕のせいでも
Whether it's your fault or mine
どちらでも Got Cheat
Either way, Got Cheat
確かめなよ相性
Verify our compatibility
ただ求めて欲しい
I just want you to desire me
バレるまで過ち
A mistake until caught
余所見はしないでいい？
Is it okay if you don't look away?
Guilty Pleasure
棘もっと這わせて
Let the thorns crawl more
もっと先まで
Go even further
Guilty Pleasure
鍵もっと回して
Turn the key more
もっと言わせて
Make me say it more
こじ開けちゃったよ
I've pried it open
僕を慰めている Toy
A toy that's comforting me
思考焼き切れるまで High
High until thoughts burn out
いけるところまで行かせて
Let me go as far as I can
触れる禁断...
Touching the forbidden...
熟れる禁断　そう破ってる　Got Cheat
The forbidden fruit is ripe, and I'm breaking it, Got Cheat
君はどこにでもいる Boy
You are everywhere, Boy
なのに胸がヒリつく Why?
But why does my chest sting?
いけるとこまでいかせて
Let me go as far as I can
揺れる輪郭　もう満ちてる　Got Cheat
The swaying silhouette is already full, Got Cheat
これはありふれている Lick
This is just an ordinary lick
だけど繰り返したい Words
But I want to repeat the words
いけるとこまでいかせて
Let me go as far as I can
甘い誘惑　癖になってる　Got Cheat
The sweet temptation is becoming a habit, Got Cheat
Oh...
君のせいでも　僕のせいでも
Whether it's your fault or mine
Oh...
Oh 何度でも Got Cheat
Oh, as many times as it takes, Got Cheat
はい、ということで皆様
Alright, everyone!
この後はMV
After this, the music video...
プラスメン限ライブ楽しむぞー！
...plus the members-only live, let's enjoy it!
それでは移動
Now, let's head over...
レッツゴー！
...let's go!
あ、勝手に飛ばされるんで
Oh, you'll be redirected automatically...
大丈夫ですよ
...so it's okay.
そのまま、いってらっしゃい！
Just stay there and enjoy the show!
Got Cheat
癒月ちょこ生誕祭2024
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2024
重大告知あり！
Important announcement!